{"data":[{"question":"He is my son,___ a better son does not exist.","a":"but","b":"than who","c":"against whom","d":"than whom","answer":"4","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Than: used when comparing two things, people, situations etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher ___ is at that desk over there.","a":"you should talk to","b":"you are talk to","c":"whom you talking to","d":"you to whom will talk","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- You should talk to = Whom you should talk to\n\n- \"You are talk to\" and \" whom you talking to\" are incorrect in gramma which should be \" are taking to\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ is more time.","a":"That what we need","b":"What we are needing","c":"What we need","d":"Which we need","answer":"3","explain":"\n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"President Lee greeted Chen Yi An, ___ a gold medal at the Olympic Games.","a":"by winning","b":"the winning","c":"she was the winner of","d":"who was the winner of","answer":"4","explain":"\n-We use relative clauses to postmodify a noun - to make clear which person or thing we are talking about. \n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Mac Arthur controls a thousand men, ___ must obey his orders in both war and peace.","a":"all of whom","b":"all of who","c":"all them","d":"all of which","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Insulin is perhaps the drug ___ more lives than any other in the history of medicine.","a":"which saved","b":"who saves","c":"which has saved","d":"what has saved","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"As many members ___ were present agreed to the plan.","a":"who","b":"that","c":"which","d":"as","answer":"4","explain":"\n- As ... as: used when you are comparing two people, things, situations etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Avoid such insects ___ will do you harm.","a":"as","b":"but","c":"who","d":"which","answer":"1","explain":"\n- As: used to state why a particular situation exists or why someone does something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He was a foreigner, ___ they perceived from his accent.","a":"that","b":"what","c":"as","d":"whom","answer":"3","explain":"\n- As: used to state why a particular situation exists or why someone does something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___, he played truant from school yesterday.","a":"That is often the case with an idle boy","b":"As is often the case with an idle boy","c":"Which is often the case for an idle boy","d":"What is often the case for an idle boy","answer":"2","explain":"\n- As: used to say that what you are saying is already known or has been stated before","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}